Viewers all over the world, whatevery situation you are in,
whatever challenges, it is darkness.
I command light!
Let there be light, in the name of Jesus!
In your health - let there be light!
In your kidneys - let there be light!
In your liver - let there be light!
In your blood - let there be light!
In your organs - let there be light!
Wherever it is located - let there be light!
Let there be light!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
That setback - let there be light!
That disappointment - let there be light!
That failure - let there be light!
That infirmity - let there be light!
Let there be light!
That nightmare - let there be light!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see the light of God!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name